

# Enrico Liscio

PhD researcher

#### Personal Details

Date of birth 20/09/1993

City Delft, the Netherlands e-mail enrico.liscio@gmail.com Telephone (+31) 6 53524819

## Personal Description

I truly believe that AI is an outstanding technology that can and must be used to help society progress. So that is what I set out to do: **research and develop** AI that can support people in having better online discussions. And I enjoy **divulging** it with videos for lay-people. Furthermore, as actor and former board member of an improvisational theatre association, I learned **organizational** and **communication** skills. Curiosity keeps me alive: **learning** something new brightens my days.

# Working experience

2020-present **PhD researcher**, *TU Delft*, Topic: personal values estimation in value-sensitive deliberation. Use NLP to extract individuals' values from text while deliberating about a topic of discussion.

2017-2020 **Deep learning and computer vision developer**, *Fizyr*, Delft RoboValley, development and implementation of state-of-the-art deep learning algorithms to solve vision challenges in automation and logistics industry.

2016-2017 **Graduate intern**, *Heemskerk Innovative Technology*, Delft RoboValley, development of autonomous robotic grasping of objects in cluttered environments.

#### Education

2015–2017 **Cum laude MSc**, *TU Delft*, *Final grade: 9/10*. Systems and Control (with the Robotics Institute Excellence Scholarship)

2012–2015 **Cum laude BSc**, *Università degli studi di Bologna*, *Final grade: 110L/110*. Automation Engineering

# Awards

2015–2017 Excellence Scholarship, TU Delft Robotics scholarship, Robotics institute.

2011–2014 Excellence Scholarship, ENASARCO scholarship, ENASARCO.

# Softwares proficiency

Keras	••••	Python	••••	ROS	••••
TensorFlow	••••	C++	••••	Linux	••••
OpenCV	•••00	MatLab	••••	<b>Δ</b> Τ <sub>Ε</sub> Χ	••••

## Languages

Italian Mothertongue

## Extra-Curricular Activities

2015-2020 Improvisational theatre, Delft Improv Group, improviser.

2016-2018 Board member, Delft Improv Group, chairman.

2016-2018 Volleyball/Basketball, D.S.V.V. Punch, player.

2016 **Coach**, *TU Delft*, coaching and leading new incoming students to the university in their summer welcoming Introduction Programme.